

Akos Radler

Phone:

+36 50 105 8216

Email: akos.radler@gmail.com

About me

Full stack web developer with 11 years of experience in various industries. Enthusiastic, always keen to learn about technologies and sharing it with others. I work best in highly collaborative environments, as I believe great communication is crucial for successful projects. My free time is usually spent playing squash, traveling, or hiking with friends.

Experience



Technical Lead

Infinitas Learning
Jun 2023 – Jun 2024
Utrecht, Netherlands (Remote)













React GitHub NodeJS Mongo TypeScript Azure

As a technical lead at Infinitas, I lead a small team of 3, supporting a rather complex web application component, which was responsible for displaying and scoring student exercises. During my time, I used my knowledge on bundlers to cut build times for better DX, migrated our pipelines to GitHub workflows, made strides in TypeScript conversions, and mentored my less experienced colleagues, all the while meeting the vision and goals of business.



Senior Full Stack Developer

Danubius Informatika Sep 2020 – Jun 2023 Budapest, Hungary (Remote)













React GitHub NodeJS GraphQL MUI Azure

At Danubius, we took on rebuilding an international company's educational platform from the ground up. A rewarding task, as it would help kids on their learning journey in 3 different countries. Even though we were a team of peers, I frequently mentored less experienced teammates, and acted as a drop-in engineering manager whenever I needed to be.



Senior Frontend Developer (contract)

Inflex Studio
Oct 2019 – Apr 2020
Budapest, Hungary (Remote)



N EV/E



React

Next is

I worked at Inflex Studio as a frontend developer, where we delivered various web applications for various small businesses. These included small customizable CRMs and project management systems. The company was fully remote from the beginning, to which I found no problem adjusting.



Full Stack Developer

Totaljobs Group Oct 2018 – Jun 2019

Oct 2018 – Jun 2019 London, United Kingdom











.Net

AWS

TypeScript React

Microsoft SQL Server

I joined a scrum team of 5 at TotalJobs, as a part of their tribe system. I was mainly focused on improving the company's flagship email delivery system, to which our team made various enhancements in terms of scaling and availability, in order for it to be able to function as a service for other teams as well. I also took part in building an AWS based Job-SMS system, which our team delivered to tens of thousands of people.



.Net Engineer

Coyote Software
Jul 2018 – Oct 2018
London, United Kingdom











.Net

Azure

Octopus TeamCity

Microsoft SQL Server

At Coyote, we worked on bringing modern day solutions to people in the proptech industry. The company's cloud-based web application helps real estate experts buy, sell, research, market, and manage industrial properties to this day.



.Net Server Developer

Derivco

Sep 2016 – Jul 2018 Ipswich, United Kingdom









.Net

Microsoft Orleans

Docker RabbitMQ

My role was server developer in the sports betting industry. Part of a scrum team of 6, I was mainly responsible for making sure that our actor-model based distributed system scales, and performs under heavy user load. I also took part in enhancing various internal applications which were used to monitor the behaviours and performance of our system.



.Net Software Developer

evosoft

Jan 2014 – Aug 2016 Budapest, Hungary



.Net

I was part of a small international development team where we developed a configuration, and runtime monitoring application for SIEMENS smart devices, written in C#. The team was partially based in Germany, to which we made regular visits in order to aid team collaboration.

Education



Eötvös Loránd University

Bachelor's Degree, Computer Science 2008 – 2012